{
    "subject": "resource/N._D._Cocea",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Satire",
    "human_readable": "N. D. Cocea's genre is Satire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9342140555381775,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in N. D. Cocea's satire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9082289934158325,
            "question": "Compare and contrast N. D. Cocea's style with other satirists."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8582428693771362,
            "question": "What makes N. D. Cocea's satire effective?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7396129965782166,
            "question": "What genre of writing is N. D. Cocea known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722879946231842,
            "question": "What impact has N. D. Cocea's satire had on readers or society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5533061623573303,
            "question": "Why is satire an important literary genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4468214511871338,
            "question": "Are there any historical or social contexts that influence N. D. Cocea's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40394243597984314,
            "question": "Give an example of a work by N. D. Cocea."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36644813418388367,
            "question": "How would you describe the tone of N. D. Cocea's writing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35359469056129456,
            "question": "How does N. D. Cocea use humor in their writing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=N. D. Cocea's genre is Satire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8606_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the tone of N. D. Cocea's writing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8606_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a work by N. D. Cocea.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8606_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical or social contexts that influence N. D. Cocea's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8606_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8606_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided indicates that N. D. Cocea was known as a satirist and his works, including his political novels and lampoons, are described in the context given. Therefore, the statement \"N. D. Cocea's genre is Satire\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}